Enough!
Why do you have this?
What are you doing here?
I didn't mean it.
All of a sudden, there was a fire.
Nero, calm down.
Let's find out first what happened.
Maybe all of this was just an accident.
This woman destroyed a place
that's very important to me.
I'm sure Florence didn't mean to do this.
We'll talk about this
when everyone has calmed down,
so we'll know the root of this mess.
Believe me, Grandpa,
even if I have calmed down,
I don't want to see the face of this woman.
I have a bad feeling.
Something wrong is happening.
Go and call Florencia.
The fact that she discovered your secret camp
is very impressive.
It means, she's not only cooking for you.
She's making an effort to get to know you.
I'm sorry, Grandson,
I won't agree to kick Florence out.
Because if we don't know how to forgive,
we will not have a heart
deserving of happiness
and capable of love.
Florence, have you given the rambutan?
Did the kids like it?
Yes, Mother, Father.
He liked it very much
and consumed everything.
He ate a lot.
Florence, you're lying.
Show yourself.
I'll make a deal with you.
Apologize to Nero first.
Now, if he can't forgive you, then resign.
I will even give you generous separation pay.
But don't give up easily.
Try it first.
Give the person a chance to forgive.
We all deserve a second chance.
What are you doing here?
Didn't I tell you
I don't want to see you anymore?
One minute... that's all I ask from you.
Just one minute.
I just want to make up
for all the kindness you did for me.
I hope when our paths cross again,
you will no longer be mad at me.
I heard Grandpa Garp is making
Florence apologize to Nero.
Do you think Nero will forgive her?
I don't think so, because knowing Nero,
he's one of the toughest guys that I know.
Let's make a bet.
Let's see who will win.
Hello?
Hello, Don Rogelio. Sir.
This is Mark.
I've already run the aging program
that I told you about,
the picture of Baby Celestina.
I've emailed you a picture
of how she will possibly look like
in 17 years.
All right.
Thank you.
Alyanna, I need your help.
If your daughter Celestina is still alive,
you've got to help me.
Point me in the right direction.
Or better yet,
let our paths cross so I can save her.
And give her the life
that you dreamed for her.
Please, Alyanna...
Show me where your daughter is.
Mother and Father,
I'm also excited to go out.
I've been here for a long time.
Well, Florence,
whatever you want to do, we'll do it.
Whatever you want to eat, we'll eat it.
Everything you want to buy,
we'll buy to make you happy.
Mother, Father, as long as I'm with you,
I'm already happy.
Wow.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Ouch, ouch...
My favorite, fried chicken!
Hey, Federico, that's not allowed.
Your heart will be fried, what's with you?
Here, I brought something for you.
That's delicious.
Here's some more.
Dessert.
Mother, that's so sad.
Vegetables for dessert?
Okay, go ahead and tolerate each other.
Not even just a little?
- No.
- Just one bite, Mother?
- Florence.
- It is not allowed.
Don't worry, I'm doing okay.
If there's something I can teach you
and you can apply it in your life,
it is that all you need is a little imagination.
Imagination?
The chicken is delicious.
By the way, Mother, and Father,
here's my salary for you.
Huh?
Oh my!
Florence, this is a lot.
Did you save some for yourself?
For your school?
Mother, don't think about me,
I don't have to spend so much on school.
According to the dean,
almost everything
is shouldered by the school.
That's why I'm okay.
Florence, thank you for your sacrifices.
Father, I'm not the only one
making sacrifices for us.
And like what you said just now,
what we need in life is a little imagination.
That's why every day I imagine
that I've graduated already,
and that I've fulfilled
all our dreams in life.
Florence, is there anything else you need?
Uniforms? Don't you need uniforms?
Mother, Father, there's no uniform in GU.
Initially, I thought I have to wear a uniform
because most of the schools have that, right?
But the dean said to me,
they don't want to destroy
the right of the student
to their own individuality
and their freedom of expression.
That's why, they don't insist on
wearing a uniform in the school.
You should be who you are
when you go to school
and this can help students gain confidence
and they can build their self-image.
- GU is really good.
- They're the best.
Florence, have you imagined
what you'd look like in school?
Not yet. I'm still thinking about it.
Well, I'll help you with that.
I know a perfect spot.
- We'll go shopping.
- Shopping!
Let's eat first.
What's that?
Hey, Federico, I told you that's not allowed.
Here, have this.
- Yummy.
- It's delicious.
- I want that.
- One more.
I want that.
Hey, hey...
I already told you that's not allowed.
Just eat this.
My child... My child.
Tada!
This is the best place
to find your self-image
- and individuality.
- Hello.
What are you looking for?
So are you ready, Florence?
Yes, Mother. I'm ready to shop till we drop.
So, what now?
Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Let's go. Where will we start?
Let's start here.
Let's go there.
Which of the two do you like, Florence?
This one, Mother. There.
- Look, Florence.
- This one suits you.
This is so much like you.
Prof, pick me.
I know the answer.
- Pick me.
- Me!
- See, this is okay, right?
Father, you look like Mother
with that outfit.
Yes, that's possible.
You look just like me.
This is beautiful.
It looks perfect on you.
There you go.
Father, let me borrow this.
Let's put this on mother.
Wow.
My child, why don't you introduce to me
the girl you're with?
- The girl is beautiful, Father.
- Hey, you're something else.
Your daughter is here. Later.
Here, Florence...
- It's beautiful.
- Mother.
Isn't it too short?
- No, if this fits me...
- But, Mother, my tummy will show.
No. This is beautiful, Florence.
- I'll just pair it
- This suits you really well.
- with a high-waist skirt.
- Yes, that's perfect.
- And then I'll wear a cardigan on it.
- And this too, it's beautiful also.
This is better, Mother.
- The other one is too short.
- It's good.
Believe me, Florence...
- Hey, this is okay.
- This is okay.
Father!
- This looks good...
- Father?
- What?
- Federico!
- What are you wearing?
I just tried it on because it suits you.
Everything, right?
- That outfit is for me, Father?
- Yes.
Father, since when did I wear hoops?
Why? It's okay?
- What's up?
- Hey, Federico!
Did you pay for that already?
- Oh my!
- I forgot.
- Hurry. Pay for it.
- Hurry, Father.
They might ask us for payment.
Your father is something else.
Why are you arrogant?
So now I'm arrogant?
- Do you have a problem with me?
- You're been acting rude for a while now.
- That's you.
Do you want us to fight here?
- And now it's me?
- Do you want?
Okay, let's finish this now.
- What?
- James...
- James, what's going on?
- You're so arrogant.
He's so boastful.
- Look. He's so arrogant.
- And I'm the boastful one?
What's happening here?
Nothing, Don Rogelio.
This guy is so arrogant.
Garpidio.
Rogelio.
Let's go, Baste.
You will never win with people
who don't know how to admit their mistakes.
James, let's go.
You cannot win an argument with people
who cannot accept defeat.
They'll just insist that they're right.
We bought so much stuff.
Where to next?
- Let's try here?
- Over there.
- That's a good place.
- Let's try this way.
Where should we go?
- Over there.
- There's a lot of good stuff there.
Don Rogelio, where are you going?
Excuse me.
Excuse me...
Yes, Sir?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were Celestina.
Okay.
Don Rogelio, do we have a problem?
Are you looking for someone?
No.
Come on, let's go home.
It's so cold.
- Just leave your umbrellas there.
- Okay.
Oh my God. We're all wet.
It's embarrassing.
Florence...
thanks for all your help to us.
Florence, next week, let's do this again.
We miss you so much.
Yes, Mother, me too. I miss you so much.
And the way I miss you,
it's like kage bunshin technique.
I miss you times two,
times two, times two, times two.
Well, Florence, if you need anything,
just let us know.
We'll be here right away.
I know that.
And I'm not afraid wherever I go.
I can do anything
because I know you and Father
are always there to back me up.
Of course.
Good thing you know.
And because of that...
- Goodbye hug.
- Love you!
- Love you, Mother.
- You take care of yourself here.
- Yes, Mother.
- I love you, my child.
- I love you, Father.
Always remember that.
Take care and don't get wet.
It's embarrassing.
- Bye, my child.
- Bye, Mother. Take care.
Take care, Mother and Father.
Well, well, well.
You're back.
Yes, Ms. Serafica.
I bought something for you.
I remembered you.
People wearing that are cool,
like Ms. Gretchen Barretto level.
I'll make it up to you next time.
I couldn't find any.
That's okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Florence, Dencio will bring
the boys to school tomorrow.
And James, the other driver
will drive you to school.
Me? He'll bring me to school?
- Yes.
- No need, Ma'am Serafica.
I don't want the people in school
to think that I'm rich too.
Are you sure?
Yes. Don't worry.
I'll manage.
Grandpa Garp has already
offered a lot of help.
I can go to school on my own,
so I won't disturb you and Mr. James.
Okay, if that's your decision.
- Ma'am Serafica?
- All right.
I also want to thank you.
I appreciate what you're doing
for me right now.
Oh, by the way, Florence.
What?
Good luck.
I'm rooting for you.
I hope all your dreams will come true.
Thank you.
You can retire now.
Goodnight.
- Goodnight.
- I'll make it up to you
when there are new arrivals,
so that it'll be good.
Goodnight.
Good Morning, Florence.
Are you ready to conquer the world?
Mr. Dove.
What's my letter for today?
Hey, you might hit your head.
Thank you, Mr. Dove.
Break a leg, see you at school.
Break a leg.
Are you ready, Florence?
If you're ready give me an F.
Give me an L.
Give me an O, R, E, N, C, E!
I'm Florence Dela Cruz
and I'm going to school.
I'm best in math,
and of all the good things I can do,
I can be your friend!
Go, Florence! Go!
So, guys, we're on our own for now.
Look at what we have here, Aira.
Nero looks as hot as ever.
If you compare it to tennis,
he is a Nadal, a Djokovic,
and a Federer.
He occupies all my top three.
And my fourth and fifth.
And look at Tristan.
Has he been working out?
Looks like there's a lot of stuff that grew
and became hard on him.
Do you want to have lunch together?
Aren't you tired of that?
Exactly.
We've been eating together the whole summer.
Maybe this is a welcome respite
from all that...
cheesiness.
Not to mention... Aldus is still being Aldus.
You're right about that.
I'll take Aldus any time of the day.
Not to mention, Owen.
Exactly, there's nothing we can say.
We're out of words.
I disagree but yes,
it's like I don't want to see your faces.
And look at Troy,
he seems like he is his usual fun self.
I like some fun.
Do you like some fun, Aira?
I was born to be fun.
How about you, Nero?
I don't know any of you.
So, let's go.
[Gyronella University]
Hot.
What in the name of?
What is that?
Look at her.
Mister, I'll get off here.
Next time again.
Here's my payment. Take care.
Oh my God.
Mother, Father, this is it!
I'm here in GU.
I'll do my best for our future.
This is the first day
for the rest of our lives.
This is the start
of a new chapter of success!
Please go to our booth.
Booth?
Okay.
Looks like our beloved university
has a new charity case.
You can say that again.
Should we put her on our blacklist?
Looks like it'll be fun
to play a prank on her.
Let's not waste our time.
Besides, we still have one more target.
And we need to focus our time on her.
And from what I heard,
she's not following our orders.
Looks like we need to teach her a lesson.
I agree.
Yeah, for sure.
- I have a lot.
- Please go to our booth.
Okay.
I have a lot of places to go.
[Gyronella University]
What do you think happened
for me to deserve this?
Miss, where is the Com Arts Building?
Just follow the people.
Wow, great.
Just follow the people. All right.
You think you're being smart?
Stop acting like you belong here.
No one likes you.
If your parents didn't win the lottery,
I doubt you can even afford to be here.
Exactly.
But it doesn't mean that
just because you can pay the tuition here,
you can pretend like you're one of us.
You will never be one of us.
True.
You can dress well.
You can buy expensive stuff,
but inside you're still garbage.
True.
Exactly.
What are you doing?
Look who's here.
The new attention-seeker.
Shoo, girl, shoo!
Mind your own business, please.
Do you know my father's favorite saying?
The way to the heart of a man or woman
is through their stomach.
What?
- She's kidding.
- What are you talking about?
But I don't think that applies to you
because it seems like your tummy
and intestines are not good.
It looks like there's a blockage
going to your heart as well.
So, what's more applicable to you is...
"the only thing necessary
for the triumph of evil
is for good men to do nothing."
And with cases like this
that you're bullying someone
and there's a witness like me
when we won't do anything and be quiet...
Oops!
What? You'll take a video of me?
No.
[Dean]
Dean!
There are students here
who are bullying someone.
I pity the girl,
she's on the verge of tears, Dean.
- Let's go, girls!
- There are five of them.
They think they're so brave.
Hey, wait, where are you going?
That's just a joke. Don't be scared.
I didn't really call the dean.
And if it's true that I called him,
there's no reason for you to be scared.
You're the one being bullied.
They should be the one's who are worried.
I'm Florence by the way.
What are you doing?
Do you have any idea what you just did?
Yes, I saw them picking on you,
so I scared them,
so they'll stop bullying you.
Obviously, you're new here.
You don't know who you're fighting with.
Next time, just mind your own business, okay?
Because of what you did,
you just made my situation worse.
So be careful
because you'll also get in trouble
and it seems that they'll pick on you next.
What do you think happened
for me to deserve this?
That's bad.
How is the view from the floor?
Why do you keep on changing your clothes?
It's none of your business.
Hey!
What are you looking at?
Owen, please, don't cramp my style.
Why are you here?
We've already talked
and we don't know each other.
Her name is Sophia.
Her family owns a coffee shop chain
and I think they have a farm in Batangas.
She's my classmate in Russian Literature.
She owes me.
I helped her deconstruct Dostoyevsky.
Do you want me to introduce you?
Or never mind,
since we don't know each other?
What do you need?
I'm just worried about Florence.
Stop acting like her boyfriend.
I'm not acting like her boyfriend.
But have you seen what she looks like?
Yeah, she was just being herself.
Exactly, she's being herself,
so she's painting herself as a target.
It's like she's seeking attention
so the rich and obnoxious students
can pick on her.
How dare you suggest that I'm evil.
What do you know?
That I'm the villain in this story?
I told you.
The first time I saw her,
it looks like this one is bad news.
You want attention, right?
Now, we'll pay attention to you.
The good news is, I am here to warn you.
The bad news is,
I'm also about to destroy you.
Correction, we are about to destroy you.
We will make sure that
your life here will be hell.
And it will be so bad that
you don't have any choice
but to transfer to a new school.
Right.
So, good luck.
- Deserve.
Let's go, girls.
We should've asked her to come with us.
So this whole university knows
she's one of us...
and no one will try to bother her.
You know that's one thing she hates the most.
Have you forgotten how many times
she reminded you
that when we get to the university,
we don't know each other?
Hey, you Ferell guys,
when we get to the school,
we don't know each other.
You don't know me, and I don't know you too.
Why? Because the students there
might think that I'm as arrogant
and hard-headed as all of you.
That's why she refused
to hitch a ride with us,
no matter how hard we tried to convince her.
And do you really think that will help her?
There are a lot of people
who are jealous of us, Ferells.
And being associated with us
might not be so good for her.
And for sure,
people will start asking questions.
Like, who is she?
Why is she connected with us?
Why is Grandpa sending her to school?
And I'm sure this can create
an issue for our family.
And the last we need
is another rumor against our family.
I still worry about Grandpa's heart.
I know that,
but are we really letting Florence be?
Rich people are the worse.
Sooner or later, someone will target her.
It's just a matter of time before someone
makes her life here a nightmare.
It's like this, Bro.
Look at it this way.
Maybe the people here at the University
should worry about Florence.
What do you mean?
Do you think Florence is the kind of person
who will just let others step on her?
Do you think that Florence
is the type of person...
who will not fight back
if someone is trying to oppress her?
If there's one person who can fight back,
that's Florence.
Because in the short period
that we've known her,
she's the kind of person
who you can't destroy
even if you hit her several times.
Hey!
You already saw that I fell,
and now you're asking me
to hold on to your drink?
You're really useless.
You want me to throw your garbage.
Ah, so he's sweet...
So that's why.
You better hurry because
Don Ferell is about to eat.
Don't forget the water, please.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Good morning, Don Ferell.
- Good morning.
- Your breakfast is ready.
Who cooked? You?
No, Sir. It was still Florence.
Huh? How?
Well, she woke up early to prepare.
As a matter of fact,
she already cooked your lunch.
And she left me detailed instructions
on how to heat up your food.
Very good girl.
She's special.
She deserves it.
She totally deserves it.
Yeah, I mean we were
minding our own business,
and then she suddenly meddles.
Exactly.
She's not aware of her place here.
She labeled us as if we were
the villains in her life.
Well, if that's what she believes,
then I guess we should play the part.
- I agree.
- Right?
Embrace our roles
as the villains in the life of that squatter.
Oh.
Are you guys thinking of what I'm thinking?
Yes.
We are so sisters to the top of Everest
because I can read what you want.
Yeah.
I think it's time to use our network.
Aylip's network of horror.
Game?
Game. What are we waiting for?
[TWPS]
Nice.
So, what do you think?
That looks awesome, Ash.
Very promising idea.
It will be our University's official channel.
I'll make content about our university,
everything GU.
I'll review our food here in the cafeteria,
news about school activities,
and places to hang out in GU.
And of course, a profile piece...
of the coolest students
here in the university, like us.
Why are you telling me this?
Well, the truth is, I need a partner.
As much as I want to,
it's not just my face that will carry this.
I need the gravitas of a Ferell
so there's someone who will watch my content.
No.
No, straight away?
Think about it.
I go live tonight
and you can join me anytime.
I'm sorry, Ash...
but that's not my cup of tea.
The last thing I want to do
is face the camera.
What about... what about him?
That's even more difficult.
I don't think that's possible.
Why so?
And I heard, he was dating
the most beautiful girl on campus.
What happened to them?
Oh my Gosh.
Looks like it's just the first day of school
and something major is happening.
Major event?
Well, I heard a rumor
that there's this secret sorority
of popular girls on campus.
They are known by the name Aylip.
Aylip?
Yes, they're a very powerful group.
As in, only the cream of the crop is invited.
These are children of the wealthiest family,
student leaders, and top academic listers.
And, if the rumors are correct,
if you offend any one of them,
it's like you offended all of them.
And, based on my sources...
there's someone new that they're declaring
persona-non-grata on the first day of school.
Who?
[TWPS]
Oh?
Hey! Owen, wait. We're not yet done talking.
Alyanna...
I saw a girl who looks exactly like you
the other day.
I don't believe in what they say
"leap of blood" but...
I felt something.
Is she my grandchild?
Is Celestina alive?
Because if she is,
I will not stop until I find her.
Are they looking at me?
Is there dirt on my face?
Well, right...
Marian Rivera...
Left, Bea Alonzo.
Go ahead and get tired of at looking me.
I'm sure you find me beautiful.
Goodbye.
Move aside.
What's with my face?
Is there really dirt?
I'll just use the CR.
This is off-limits.
Off-limits?
Why?
I said... this is off-limits.
Shoo.
Okay, I'll use a different comfort room.
Girl...
Did you do that on purpose?
If you don't want to be hit,
find a different place,
not here where we are playing.
Hey!
Who are you?
Let go of me.
Have you seen Florence?
Florence is missing?
Did you receive my messages?
What message?
I haven't received anything from you.
You suddenly disappeared.
You're right.
This would be better for both of us.
How's Florence?
Well, she sent me a message.
She said she was just fixing something.
I'll just go here. There's a way here.
Why are you following me?
Show yourself.
Do you think I'm scared of you?
Who are you?